[
  {
    "question": "What is the function to calculate the sum of a range of cells?",
    "correct_answer": "Sum",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Average",
      "MIN",
      "MAX"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"cell address\" refer to in Excel?",
    "correct_answer": " The intersection of a column and a row.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "The location of a cell in a row",
      "The formatting of a cell",
      "The name of a worksheet."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Excel feature allows you to apply formatting based on specific criteria?",
    "correct_answer": "Conditional Formatting",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Data Validation",
      "Pivot Tables",
      "Goal Seek"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the \"Freeze Panes\" feature in Excel?",
    "correct_answer": " To lock specific rows or columns from scrolling",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "To hide sensitive data.",
      "To protect the worksheet from editing.",
      "To create a drop-down list."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function to convert text to uppercase in Excel?",
    "correct_answer": "LOWER",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "PROPER",
      "UPPER",
      "TEXT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the IF function in Excel do?",
    "correct_answer": "It creates conditional statements.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "It performs mathematical calculations.",
      "It generates random numbers.",
      "It formats cells."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the keyboard shortcut to insert a new row in Excel",
    "correct_answer": "Ctrl + +",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ctrl + -",
      "Ctrl + Shift + =",
      "Ctrl + ="
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you remove duplicate values in a column in Excel?",
    "correct_answer": "Use the \"Remove Duplicates\" feature",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Apply a filter",
      "Sort the column in ascending order",
      "iManually delete duplicates"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the \"Goal Seek\" feature in Excel?",
    "correct_answer": "To find the input value needed to achieve a desired output.",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "To find the maximum value in a range.",
      "To determine the minimum value in a range.",
      "To calculate the average of a range."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function to find the smallest value in a range of cells?",
    "correct_answer": "MAX",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "MIN",
      "AVERAGE",
      "SUM"
    ]
  }
]